Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - Abdülhamid II clock tower, Jaffa Gate., Circa 1908 - 1922; ref245; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Clocks/Watches; Men; Women; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Street Lamps; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Palestine; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills
  - View of a town from above., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref246; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 X 9.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Landscapes; Buildings; Construction
  - Sabongi Brothers (Bawaky St, Cairo) studio card., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref247; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.9 X 12.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mansoura, Egypt; Cairo, Egypt; Postal Stamps; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Printed Materials
  - Group portrait of Nasri Fuleihan (right), Ismail Bey el Husseini, Salim Ayoub, F. Karam (camp contractor) and members of survey party (rodmen) Antoun Mouchabik, Hanna Hamami, L. Lorenzo (linked ref234)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref248; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 14.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Umbrellas/Parasols; Flags; Tents; English Writing; Civil Engineering
  - View of a village from above., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref249; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes; Houses; Palm Trees
  - Solomon's Stables, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref250; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.1 X 9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Palestine
  - Two men in front of stone wall by the Zawiya of Rabi'a al-'Adawiyya (Mosque of the Ascension)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref251; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Chapel of the Ascension; Religious Sites; Men; Regional/National Dress; Buildings; Mosques; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - Two people on a hillside overlooking Hebron., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref253; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Buildings; Men; Horses; Animals; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Palestine; Religious Sites; Hats; Group Portraits; Mountains/Hills; English Writing
  - A man standing against a column in the Church of the Nativity, Bethlehem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref252; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 X 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bethlehem; Churches; Church of the Nativity; Palestine; Men; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a woman, text on reverse "Ramallah girl"., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref254; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ramallah; Women; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Embroidery; Jewelry; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Palestine
  - A man standing in the columbarium between el Mudawwara and Durusiya. Text on reverse "Cave 3 miles north east of Dayr Nakhkhas"., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref255; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.4 X 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin); Caves; Men; Hats; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palestine
  - Group portrait of three men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref256; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.4 X 11.6cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Smoking; Tobacco pipes
  - A person being assisted into a boat with other people., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref257; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Boats/Ships; Seas; Girls; Children; Hats; Water; Group Portraits
  - Group portrait of a woman and four men on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref258; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Bow Ties; Umbrellas/Parasols; Cigarettes; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Smoking; Palestine
  - Group portrait of men and women on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref259; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Jewelry; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Dogs; Animals; Palestine; Medals/Insignia
  - Group portrait of men and women on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref260; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Men; Women; Buildings; Hats; Group Portraits; Jewelry; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Palestine
  - Group portrait of two women and three men on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref261; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Men; Women; Umbrellas/Parasols; Bow Ties; Fez/Tarboush; Group Portraits; Palestine; Hotels; Hats
  - Man standing next to a dog., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref262; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Dogs; Animals; Individual Portraits
  - Group portrait of men and women sitting around a table in a garden., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref263; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Bow Ties; Agriculture/Farms; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Gardens; Outdoors
  - Portrait of man and woman on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref264; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jerusalem; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Men; Women; Buildings; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - Three men and two women posing by a waterfall in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref265; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 12.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Waterfalls; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Jordan
  - Acacia tree at Birket ez Zuweira (Zohar), Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref266; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; Palestine; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Agriculture/Farms
  - People posing in front of a tent (linked 205)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref267; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Tents; Men; Women; Boys; Children; Donkeys; Animals; Group Portraits; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Bow Ties
  - Group portrait of three women., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref268; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.4 X 11.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Jewelry
  - Group portrait of women and men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref269; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.3 X 12 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Fez/Tarboush
  - Group portrait of women and men sitting in a garden., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref270; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.7 X 10.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Buildings; Facial Hair; Cigarettes; Jordan
  - Group portrait of a woman and four men in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref271; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Women; Hats; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Head Covers/Veils; Jordan; Cigarettes; Smoking
  - Men standing on a mountain top in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref272; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Jordan
  - Spring deposits near Hammam Ma'in, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref273; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 15 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; Ma'in, Jordan; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Springs
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref274; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills
  - A letterhead from The Middle East Enterprise Company Engineers, 299 Madison Avenue, New York 17, New York, U.S.A. Telephone Murray Hill 2-4239., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref275; 1 Photographic Prints; 27.6 X 21.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Printed Materials; English Writing; New York, USA; Civil Engineering; Offices; United States of America
  - Studio photograph envelope: Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, G.P.O. Box 72, Jaffa Road, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref276_000001; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.3 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Printed Materials; English Writing; Jerusalem; Studio Photography; Advertisements; Palestine
  - Studio photograph envelope: Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, G.P.O. Box 72, Jaffa Road, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref276_000002; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.3 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Studio photograph envelope: Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, G.P.O. Box 72, Jaffa Road, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref276_000003; Hanania Brothers, Photographic Specialists, Jaffa Road, G.P.O. Box 72, Jerusalem (Palestine); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.3 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Studio photograph envelope: C. Raad, Photographer, (near Allenby Hotel) Jerusalem., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref282; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 X 15 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Printed Materials; English Writing; Jerusalem; Studio Photography; Palestine
  - Group portrait of two women, a man and baby (linked ref284, 285), Circa 1910s -1930s; ref283; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.1 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - Group portrait of a man and woman (linked ref283, 285), Circa 1910s -1930s; ref284; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Jewelry; Unknown Locations
  - Group portrait of a man and woman holding a child (linked ref283, 384)., Circa 1910s -1930s; ref285; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Exterior of a building (linked ref287)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref286; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 11.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Houses; Buildings; Agriculture/Farms
  - Exterior of a building (linked ref286)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref287; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8 X 11.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Studio photograph envelope: C. Raad, Photographer, (near Allenby Hotel) Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref293; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 X 15 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Studio photograph envelope: C. Raad, Photographer, (near Allenby Hotel) Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref294; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 15.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Man posing in front of tent (linked ref332, 335)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref321; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Tents; Individual Portraits
  - Studio photograph envelope: C. Raad, Photographer, (near Allenby Hotel) Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref329; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 X 15.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Studio photograph envelope: C. Raad, Photographer, (near Allenby Hotel) Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref331; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 X 15.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Man posing in front of tent (linked ref321, 335)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref332; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.5 pm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Tents
  - Portrait of Nasri Fuleihan., 24 April 1919; ref333; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 X 4.1 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Signatures; Studio Photography; Painted Backdrops; English Writing; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Men
  - Nasri Fuleihan posing in front of a tent (linked ref321, 332)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref335; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.2 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Tents; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits
  - Man standing next to a cow., Circa 1910s -1939; ref337; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 X 7.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Cattle/Cows; Animals; Buildings; Hats; Individual Portraits
  - Man holding a wooden wheel., Circa 1910s -1939; ref338; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.9 X 7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Hats; Carriages/Coaches; Individual Portraits
  - Two women and a man in a carriage (linked ref341, 370)., Circa 1910s -1939; ref339; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.8 X 6.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Hats; Carriages/Coaches; Animals; Group Portraits; Buildings
  - Group portrait of men and women (linked ref342, 369)., Circa 1910s -1939; ref340; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.8 X 6.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats
  - Group of people in a carriage (linked ref339, 370)., Circa 1910s -1939; ref341; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.8 X 6.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Animals; Carriages/Coaches; Group Portraits; Buildings; Hats
  - Group portrait of men and women (linked ref340, 369)., Circa 1910s -1939; ref342; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.8 X 6.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits
  - Portrait of a man standing in open fields., Circa 1910s -1939; ref343; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - A portrait of Nasri Fuleihan (left) and another man., Circa 1910s -1939; ref344; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Group Portraits; Hats
  - Three children (including Dorothy Fuleihan, Nasri Fuleihan's daughter) in a garden., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref346; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.7 X 6.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Children; Boys; Girls; Group Portraits; Clocks/Watches
  - Landscape including a town and a plateau., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref347; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Agriculture/Farms; Buildings; Landscapes; Palestine; Houses
  - A man and a woman on the terrace of a stone building (linked ref354, 365)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref350; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Hats; Buildings; Group Portraits; Palestine
  - A group of people at a table under a canopy (linked ref352)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref351; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.3 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Clocks/Watches
  - A group of people at a table under a canopy (linked ref351)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref352; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Tents; Hats
  - Isabel Fuleihan née Oussani sitting on a cannon (linked ref357)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref353; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 X 6.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Gardens; Cannons; Women; Individual Portraits; Weapons; Statues/Sculptures
  - A man and a woman in front of a stone building (linked ref350, 365)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref354; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Hats; Buildings; Group Portraits
  - Five boats on a beach., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref355; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Boats/Ships; Seas; Beaches; Coast; Water; Landscapes
  - A man posing in front of a building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref356; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Hats
  - Isabel Fuleihan née Oussani posing in front of a cannon (linked ref353)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref357; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.8 X 4.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Women; Statues/Sculptures; Cannons
  - Nasri Fuleihan with his daughter, Dorothy., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref358; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.8 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Girls; Children; Group Portraits; Buildings
  - Dorothy Fuleihan (Nasri Fuleihan's daughter) standing next to a dog., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref359; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.8 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Girls; Children; Dogs; Animals; Toys; Individual Portraits
  - Dorothy Fuleihan (Nasri Fuleihan's daughter) holding a toy., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref360; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.7 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Children; Girls; Toys; Individual Portraits
  - Dorothy Fuleihan (Nasri Fuleihan's daughter) sitting on the ground., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref361; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.9 X 4.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Girls; Children; Individual Portraits
  - Margaret Oussani (Nasri Fuleihan's sister-in-law) in a garden., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref362; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.1 X 4.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Women; Agriculture/Farms; Hats; Individual Portraits
  - Margaret Oussani (Nasri Fuleihan's sister-in-law) in a garden., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref363; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 X 4.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Women; Hats; Agriculture/Farms; Individual Portraits
  - Statue of George Washington in the World's fair 1940., Circa 1940s; ref364; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.4 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; New York, USA; Statues/Sculptures; Fountains; Group Portraits
  - Group portrait of two men and a woman in front of a stone building (linked ref350, 354)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref365; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.6 X 4.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Men; Buildings; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits
  - Rock formations in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref366; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.1 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Jordan
  - A statue on a column in the Ashkelon/Ashqelon archaeological site (linked refs 128, 142, 143, 415)., Circa 1923 - 1930; ref367; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6 X 4.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ashḳelon/Ashqelon; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Palestine
  - Group portrait (linked ref340, 342)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref369; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 X 6.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - Two women and a man on carriage. (linked ref339, 341)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref370; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 4 X 6.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)